Mu Ko Ang Thong

Ang Thong, which means “Bowl of Gold,” is a popular national park in the Gulf of Thailand. Consisting of 42 islands, which are close together for easy island hopping, the park is headquartered on Ko Wua Talap. There, travelers can stay in lovely bungalows and take in incredible views of the surrounding islands and bizarre rock formations. Exploring the islands white sand beaches and snorkeling among the shallow coral gardens makes a popular day trip from Ko Samui.


346/1 Talad Lang, ตำบล บางกุ้ง Mueang Surat Thani District, Chang Wat Surat Thani 84000, Thailand

+66 77 420 225

9.622778, 99.675