Phanom Rung

Sitting on an extinct volcano in northeastern Thailand, Phanom Rung is a Hindu temple regarded for its outstanding architecture. Located near the village of Nang Rong, this temple sanctuary was built by the Khmer culture between the 10th and 13th centuries. Constructed of sandstone and laterite, Phanom Rung was built to represent Mount Kailash, the sacred home of Shiva.

บ้านยายแย้ม Ta Pek, Chaloem Phra Kiat District, Buri Ram 31110, Thailand

+66 44 666 251

8am-6pm

14.5325, 102.941667